

in /in/ysoftaoglu /website 🔿 /ysoftaoglu Bē /ysoftaoglu ♦ /ysoftaoglu ☑ /ysoftaoglu

Hi hy name is Yasin. I'am a front-end developer. I have +3 years experience in front-end development and I am looking for a software company that I can improve myself.

## **SKILLS**

HTML CSS Bootstrap Javascript **JQuery** NodeJS MongoDB React / React N. VueJS С

# **SOFTWARE & TOOLS**















## **LANGUAGES**

English: Mid-Level

Turkish: Native Language

### **OTHERS**

Smoking: No

Driving License: B Class

Military Service: Postponed

#### **EXPERIENCE**

June 2018 - August 2018

Statik Yazılım ¥ Front-end Developer

December 2017 - June 2018

Hizmetin.com ☑ Front-end Developer & Designer

October 2017 - December 2017

Hayal Mahsülleri Dijital Sanatlar Atolyesi Front-end Developer

2014 - 2017

Freelancer Front-end Developer

## **EDUCATION**

2015 - Present

CBU Software Engineering (3.7 / 4)

2008 - 2014

Mugla Anatolian Teacher High School (4.1 / 5)